Congratulations, you've completed our lesson on assessing data,
تهانينا، لقد انتهيتم من درس تقييم البيانات،
the second step of the data wrangling process.
الخطوة الثانية في عملية تعارض البيانات.
You visually and programmatically assessed a data set full of data quality and
لقد أجريت تقيمًا بصريًا وبرمجيًا لمجموعة بيانات مليئة بمشكلات تتعلق بجودة البيانات
tidiness issues and you caught and categorized every issue,
والترتيب وقمتم بالتقاط كل مشكلة وتصنيفها،
despite never having seen the data.
بالرغم من عدم رؤية البيانات.
Like a true detective thrown onto the case. That takes talent.
مثل المحقق الحقيقي الذي يُلقى به في قضية. هذا الأمر يتطلب موهبة.
Every dirty messy data set,
كل مجموعة بيانات سيئة وغير مرتبة،
and there are lots of them that exist in the world,
ويوجد الكثير منها في هذا العالم،
is dirty and messy in its own unique way and the
تكون سيئة وغير مرتبة بطريقة فريدة خاصة بها،
assessment strategies that you acquired in this lesson are transferable to all of them.
واستراتيجيات التقييم التي تعلمتها في هذا الدرس قابلة للتطبيق عليها جميعها.
This is a big deal. Now it's time to put these assessments into action.
هذا أمر مهم للغاية. حان الآن وقت تطبيق هذه التقييمات.
In the next lesson you're going to clean
في الدرس التالي، ستقومون بتنظيف
the same dataset and fix all of these issues using code.
نفس مجموعة البيانات وإصلاح المشكلات باستخدام الكود.
Here's where the magic happens.
هنا حيث يحدث السحر.